Inkscape is an incredible piece of
Inkscape是一件令人难以置信的
software that I've been using for over a
我已经用了一年多的软件
decade to create designs for myself and
十年来为我自己创造设计和
my clients as much as I love Inkscape
我的客户和我一样喜欢Inkscape
though there's one particular problem
尽管有一个特别的问题
that has it I'll be addressing in this
这就是我将在这篇文章中谈到的
video and I'll also be going over some
视频，我还会复习一些
solutions for working around it as well
也可以解决这个问题的解决方案
[Music]
[音乐]
this is Nick with logos by Nick comm and
我是尼克·康姆的标志尼克
in this video I'll be discussing how you
在这段视频中，我将讨论如何
can work around ink scapes in ability to
能够在水墨场景中工作，能够
generate files with the CMYK color
生成CMYK颜色的文件
profile and if you'd like to learn more
个人资料，如果你想了解更多
about how Inkscape works be sure to
关于Inkscape的工作原理，请务必
check out my Inkscape masterclass it's a
看看我的Inkscape大师课，它是一个
collection of over 60 videos where I go
收集了60多个视频，我去了哪里
over every tool and feature in Inkscape
Inkscape中的每个工具和功能
and I explain what it is and demonstrate
我解释了它是什么，并展示了
how it works I'll have a link in the
它是如何工作的，我会在
description of the video if you want to
视频描述(如果您想要
check that out so one of the biggest
看看这个，所以这是最大的
downsides of working with Inkscape is
使用Inkscape的缺点是
its inability to generate files with the
它无法使用
CMYK color profile this is problematic
CMYK颜色配置文件这有问题
when designing things for prints because
当为版画设计东西时，因为
the only colors that can be generated
唯一可以生成的颜色
with ink are colors that are within the
带有墨迹的颜色位于
CMYK color space
CMYK颜色空间
Inkscape by default works within the RGB
默认情况下，Inkscape在RGB中工作
color space these are colors that are
颜色空间这些颜色是
generated using light and are intended
用光产生的，目的是
for use on screens and other electronics
用于屏幕和其他电子设备
with digital displays because of that
与数字显示器一起使用
the RGB color space has a wider range of
RGB颜色空间具有更广泛的
colors to work with than CMYK does
要比CMYK使用更多的颜色
because light can be used to generate
因为光可以用来产生
more colors than ink n so if you create
比墨迹n更多的颜色，所以如果您创建
a design with Inkscape then you go to
一个带有Inkscape的设计，然后转到
print it chances are you're going to be
把它打印出来，你有可能会成为
using colors that are out of gamut or in
使用超出色域或超出色域的颜色
other words not within the range of what
其他不在什么范围内的话
can be created with ink most print shops
可以用油墨创建大多数印刷店
will refuse to print your document if
如果出现以下情况，将拒绝打印您的文档
this is the case because they know that
情况就是这样，因为他们知道
you're not going to be happy with the
你不会满意的
result now you may think to yourself
结果现在你可能会对自己说
okay I'll just use colors that are
好的，我就用那些
within the CMYK color space that it
在CMYK颜色空间内，它
should be fine right well not exactly
应该很好，对吧，不完全是
it's a little more complicated than just
这比仅仅是
using CMYK colors every document has a
使用CMYK颜色每个文档都有
color profile embedded within it and if
嵌入其中的颜色配置文件，并且如果
you created that document with Inkscape
您使用Inkscape创建了该文档
then it's going to have an RGB profile
然后它将有一个RGB配置文件
because that's the only format Inkscape
因为这是Inkscape唯一的格式
supports the problem with printing an
支持打印的问题
RGB document is that you're taking
RGB文件是您正在使用的
colors that were originally generated
最初生成的颜色
using light
使用灯光
and trying to reproduce them with ink
并试图用墨水复制它们
this usually results in their finished
这通常会导致它们完成
printed product having colors that look
印刷品的颜色看起来
dull and muddy and just overall
沉闷、泥泞，只是总体上
different than they did on your screen
与你屏幕上的不同
when you design them even if you made
当你设计它们的时候，即使你做了
sure to only use colors that work within
一定要只使用合适的颜色
the CMYK color space it's just not
CMYK色彩空间它不是
possible for something to look the same
可能的东西看起来是一样的
in print as it does on your screen if
打印出来，就像它在屏幕上一样，如果
you're creating it in an RGB color
您正在以RGB颜色创建它
profile and because of that a lot of
个人资料，因此有很多
print shops will immediately turn down
打印店将立即拒绝
your document if they see that it has an
如果他们看到您的文档有一个
RGB profile embedded now some print
嵌入的RGB配置文件现已打印
shops will do a spot conversion and
商店将进行现货转换和
adjust the colors for you this is
为您调整颜色，这是
actually becoming a lot more common and
实际上变得越来越普遍，
a good example of this would be Vista
Vista就是一个很好的例子
Print I've printed RGB documents with
打印我打印过的RGB文档
them in the past and the results were
他们在过去，结果是
actually pretty good but they weren't
实际上很好，但不是很好
perfect the best way to ensure that your
完美的最佳方式，确保您的
design will look the same in print as it
设计将在印刷品中看起来与它一样
does on your device is to make sure that
在您的设备上所做的是确保
your document is using a CMYK color
您的文档正在使用CMYK颜色
profile in illustrator this can be done
在Illustrator中配置文件可以执行此操作
by going to file document color mode and
通过转到文件文档颜色模式并
choosing CMYK color an affinity designer
选择CMYK颜色亲和力设计师
this can be done by going to file
这可以通过转到文件来完成
document setup clicking on the color tab
文档设置单击颜色选项卡
and choosing CMYK from the color format
并从颜色格式中选择CMYK
drop-down Inkscape however lacks the
然而，下拉Inkscape缺少
ability to do this and it's one of the
能够做到这一点，这是
biggest downsides of working with it in
在中使用它的最大缺点
my opinion designing things for print is
我的观点是为印刷品设计东西
just going to be more challenging in
只是更具挑战性的是
Inkscape but it's not impossible
Inkscape，但这并非不可能
there are some workarounds for creating
有一些解决方法可用于创建
a CMYK document from your Inkscape
Inkscape中的CMYK文档
designs and I'd like to share some of
设计和我想要分享的一些
them with you in this video now I must
他们和你在这段视频中，现在我必须
warn you in advance that these methods
事先警告您，这些方法
are far from perfect
远不是完美的
but they will get the job done and they
但他们会完成这项工作，而且他们
are better than nothing
总比什么都没有好
if you're a Linux user there's a
如果您是Linux用户，有一个
third-party extension that you can
您可以使用的第三方分机
install for Inkscape that will allow you
Inkscape的安装将允许您
to export PDF documents with a CMYK
要使用CMYK导出PDF文档，请执行以下操作
color profile the extension is called
颜色配置文件扩展名为
export PDF CMYK and I'll have a link in
导出PDF CMYK，我将在
the description for those of you who are
对在座各位的描述是
linux users and want to try it out I
Linux用户和想要尝试它的我
haven't tried it myself but I've heard
我自己还没试过，但我听说过
good things the benefit of using
好东西--使用的好处
something like this is that it allows
像这样的东西是它允许
you to export your design in an editable
您要将设计导出到可编辑的
vector format where you can manually
矢量格式，您可以手动
adjust the DPI which is also important
调整DPI也很重要
for printing documents the downside
用于打印文档的缺点
though is that you can only export a PDF
不过，您只能导出PDF
document so if your print shop requires
如果您的打印店需要
a rasterized format like jpg or TI F
光栅化格式，如JPG或TI F
you're out of luck the other downside is
你运气不好，另一个缺点是
that it's only for Linux users so those
它只适用于Linux用户，所以那些
of us on Windows and Mac are also out of
在Windows和Mac上的我们中的大多数人也没有
luck
运气
Scribus is an open-source application
Scribus是一个开源应用程序
for desktop publishing similar to Adobe
适用于类似Adobe的桌面发布
InDesign and it's available for all
InDesign，并向所有人开放
three operating systems one great thing
三个操作系统一个伟大的东西
about Scribus is that it allows you to
关于Scribus的是，它允许您
open PDF documents that were originally
打开最初的PDF文档
created with Inkscape and manually
使用Inkscape和手动创建
change the colors based on a CMYK color
基于CMYK颜色更改颜色
profile then once you're done you can
然后一旦你做完了你就可以
export your design as a PDF document and
将您的设计导出为PDF文档并
you will now have a print ready document
现在，您将拥有一个可打印的文档
with a CMYK color profile embedded I
嵌入了CMYK颜色配置文件
made an entire tutorial about how to do
做了一个关于如何做的完整教程
this a few years ago if you want to
这是几年前的，如果你想
check that out I'll have it linked into
看一下，我会把它链接到
the description of the video
视频的描述
much like the Linux extension the upside
与Linux扩展非常相似，优点是
of using Scribus is that you can get an
使用Scribus的好处是您可以获得一个
editable vector format that most print
打印最多可编辑的矢量格式
shops overwhelmingly accept the downside
绝大多数商店都接受不利的一面
though is that this only works on pure
不过，这只适用于纯
vector pads if your design uses a lot of
如果您的设计使用了大量的
Inkscape specific features like Gaussian
Inkscape特定功能，如高斯
blurs masking clipped objects filters
模糊遮罩剪辑对象滤镜
and so on they're not going to translate
以此类推，他们不会翻译
over to Scribus unfortunately in that
不幸的是，Scribus
case you'll have to generate a
情况下，您必须生成一个
rasterized PNG file and use a different
光栅化的PNG文件，并使用不同的
solution
解
Krita is an open-source design
Krita是一个开源设计
application that functions sort of like
功能类似的应用程序
a hybrid between Inkscape and it
Inkscape和It的混合体
allows you to work with and create
允许您使用和创建
vector objects but it also allows you to
向量对象，但它还允许您
paint and manipulate images as well one
绘制和处理图像也是一个
major benefit of use in Krita is that it
在Krita使用的主要好处是它
has the ability to export CMYK documents
能够导出CMYK文档
already built-in there is a catch though
虽然已经内置了，但有一个问题
you won't be able to export your design
您将无法导出您的设计
in a vector format like SVG or PDF
矢量格式，如SVG或PDF
credit does allow you to export in these
信用确实允许您在这些产品中出口
formats but unfortunately your document
格式，但不幸的是，您的文档
will be forced into having an RGB color
将被迫使用RGB颜色
profile Krita is ideal if you need a
配置文件Krita如果您需要
flattened raster format like PNG jpg and
平面化栅格格式，如PNG jpg和
TI F those formats can be exported with
可以使用以下命令导出这些格式
the CMYK color profile to do so first
CMYK颜色配置文件首先执行此操作
export your design from Inkscape as a
将Inkscape中的设计导出为
PNG file then open it up with credit
PNG文件，然后用信用打开它
then navigate to image properties and
然后导航到图像属性并
under the image color space tab select
在图像颜色空间选项卡下，选择
the CMYK option from the model drop-down
型号下拉列表中的CMYK选项
from there you can export your design in
从那里，您可以将您的设计导出到
any restor format and it will have a
任何RESTOR格式，它都会有一个
print ready CMYK color profile embedded
嵌入打印就绪CMYK颜色配置文件
another way that you can convert your
您可以通过另一种方式将您的
Inkscape document to CMYK is to use a
Inkscape文档到CMYK是使用一个
web-based color conversion service
基于Web的色彩转换服务
there's a lot of them out there but the
有很多这样的人，但是
one I'm most familiar with would be RGB
我最熟悉的是RGB
to CMYK org this allows you to take a
对于CMYK组织，这允许您使用
PNG file that you exported from Inkscape
从Inkscape导出的PNG文件
and convert it to either jpg or TI F
并将其转换为JPG或TI F
format with the CMYK color profile
使用CMYK颜色配置文件进行格式化
embedded the benefit of using a site
嵌入了使用网站的好处
like this is that it's quick and
就像这样，它很快，而且
convenient and you won't have to
很方便，而且您不必
download any additional software the
下载任何其他软件
downside though is that you're limited
但不利的一面是，你的能力有限
to only those two formats and another
仅限于这两种格式和另一种格式
problem I've noticed with web-based
我注意到了基于Web的问题
converters like this is that they tend
像这样的转换器是他们倾向于
to produce inconsistent results and you
以产生不一致的结果，而您
don't get to see how the final design
不要看到最终的设计是如何
looks before saving it I've had
在保存之前看起来我已经有了
instances where the final design looks
最终设计看起来像什么实例
so different from the original in terms
与原作有很大的不同
of color that it was hardly usable
颜色很差，很难使用
the final solution for generating a CMYK
生成CMYK的最终解决方案
document from your Inkscape design is to
来自您的Inkscape设计的文档是
simply save it as an SVG file then open
只需将其另存为SVG文件，然后打开
it up with illustrator or affinity
它带有插图或亲和力
designer and correct the colors yourself
自己设计和改正颜色
personally I think this is the best way
我个人认为这是最好的办法
to approach the CMYK problem as an
将CMYK问题作为一个
Inkscape user because it gives you the
Inkscape用户，因为它为您提供
most control with all of the other
最大的控制权与所有其他
methods I discussed you're basically
我讨论过的方法你基本上是
just taking your document and swapping
只是拿着你的文件，然后交换
out the color profile without ever
从颜色配置文件中剔除
having an opportunity to correct your
有机会纠正你的
colors once they've been converted
颜色转换后的颜色
illustrator allows you to do that though
Illustrator允许您这样做
and I have an entire tutorial about
我有一个完整的教程是关于
converting RGB colors to CMYK while
将RGB颜色转换为CMYK时
maintaining their vibrance on my other
在我的另一头保持他们的活力
channel if you want to check that out
频道，如果你想查看的话
I'll have that link in the description
我会在描述中有那个链接的
as well this is actually what I do
这也是我真正要做的
myself since Inkscape is the software
我自己，因为Inkscape就是软件
I'm most familiar with it's what I use
我最熟悉的就是我用的
for most of my design work and that does
对于我的大部分设计工作来说，这就是
include designs that are made for print
包括为打印而制作设计
once I'm finished creating my design in
在创建完我的设计后，
Inkscape I simply open it up with
我只需用Inkscape打开它
illustrator set the color mode to CMYK
Illustrator将颜色模式设置为CMYK
adjust the colors as needed and then
根据需要调整颜色，然后
export it to whatever format I'd like
将其导出为我想要的任何格式
and that's another benefit of using this
这是使用这个的另一个好处
approach you're not confined to just PDF
方法您不仅限于使用PDF
or just jpg you can save your work in
或者只使用jpg格式，您可以将工作保存在
any format imaginable and it'll have a
任何可以想象到的格式，它都会有一个
CMYK color profile embedded you can even
嵌入CMYK色彩配置文件，甚至可以
save your work directly as an
将您的工作直接保存为
illustrator file which believe it or not
信不信由你的Illustrator文件
some print shops do require the same can
一些印刷店确实需要同样的罐子
be done with affinity designer as well
也可以使用亲和力设计器
just open your Inkscape SVG change the
只需打开Inkscape SVG，更改
document color mode to CMYK adjust your
将文档颜色模式调整为CMYK
colors as needed then save your work to
根据需要选择颜色，然后将您的工作保存到
whatever format you'd like I understand
无论您想要什么格式，我都能理解
that these two applications are not free
这两个应用程序不是免费的
and because of that this may not be a
正因为如此，这可能不是一个
feasible option for some of you until
对你们中的一些人来说是可行的选择
Inkscape implements some kind of support
Inkscape实现了某种支持
for CMYK
对于CMYK
this is the best option we have and I
这是我们和我最好的选择
would highly recommend it if you are in
我强烈推荐你如果你在
a position to acquire one of these two
收购这两家公司之一的头寸
programs if not that any of the other
程序，如果不是其他任何程序
methods that were discussed in this
在本文中讨论的方法
video should work just fine that should
视频应该工作得很好
do it for today's video if you have any
为今天的视频做这件事，如果你有任何
questions leave a comment below and as
问题请在下面留下评论，并作为
always thanks for watching
永远感谢您的收看
[Music]
[音乐]